{
    "id": "ae0b7f809cf640c0af64f549350155d4",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "English ……………….. all over the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, we make the passive verb form by putting is/am/are before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is spoken",
                "has spoken",
                "has been spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6bb51b51635549988cb35af11813fac4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The show …………………….. by the audience.",
            "description": "In the present continuous tense, we make the passive form by putting is/am/are + being before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "has watched",
                "is watching",
                "is being watched"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "42ce9f9b15cd499c8b4362f176a13571"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief ……………………… by the police.",
            "description": "In the present perfect tense, we make the passive form by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has arrested",
                "has been arrested",
                "is arresting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1b9b8463aab46c992c83b03cdf74e4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The wounded man …………………….. by some boys.",
            "description": "In the past continuous tense, we make the passive verb form by putting was/were + being before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "was being helped",
                "was helping",
                "has helped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "546a8313e423462eb2531f85d7193998"
        },
        {
            "question": "Football ……………………. all over the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, we make the passive verb form by putting is/am/are before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is playing",
                "is played",
                "has played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e4ed10d524f425aad65c4c20cb0fb4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The match ……………………….. by our team.",
            "description": "In the simple future, we make the passive verb form by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "will win",
                "will be won",
                "will be winning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be962c16fd914117a16fa82b4c987167"
        },
        {
            "question": "The results ……………………… yet.",
            "description": "In the present perfect tense, we make the passive form by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "haven't announced",
                "haven't been announced",
                "isn't been announced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d578a07639b47c99b1904094c346eb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her looks ……………………….. by people.",
            "description": "In the present perfect tense, we make the passive form by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "have always admired",
                "have always been admired",
                "was always admired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9caa0fb127641849635a30dc8b22ba7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The answers ……………………. on both sides of the paper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should write",
                "should be written",
                "should be writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a07f13dce0c4a2caf464066bd32608c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured person ……………………. to hospital.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive verb form by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "was taken",
                "has taken",
                "have been taken"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "356c673bb52e4cddb47b2566348ce731"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………….. by anybody.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive verb form by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "was not invited",
                "has not invited",
                "was not inviting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "364eff1bd0724ecab1894942b4dadda6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………. by evil advisors.",
            "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive verb form by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "was surrounded",
                "has surrounded",
                "was surrounding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eefb71d0c4054098aded0cc956b045d1"
        }
    ]
}